let question = [
    {
        question: "Where does coffee come from?",
        answers:["Ethiopia", "Italy", "France", "from a nearby store"],
        correctAnswer: "Ethiopia"
    },

    {
        question: "Which is not a roasting method?",
        answers:["Spanish", "Italian", "French", "British"],
        correctAnswer: "British"
    },

    {
        question: "What color is the ripe coffee berry?",
        answers:["Yellow", "Green", "Red", "Blue"],
        correctAnswer: "Red"
    },

    {
        question: "There is really no caffeine in decaffeinated coffee?",
        answers:["Yes, it is true", "No, it is not true (decaffeinated coffee contains 2-6% caffeine)", "Maybe, it is true", "What does decaffeinated coffee mean?"],
        correctAnswer: "No, it is not true (decaffeinated coffee contains 2-6% caffeine)"
    },

    {
        question: "Where they produce the most coffee in the world?",
        answers:["Vietnam", "Brasil", "Ethiopia", "India"],
        correctAnswer: "Brasil"
    },

    {
        question: "What is not the main characteristic of robusta coffees?",
        answers:["acidic", "high in caffeine", "dark brown", "full-bodied"],
        correctAnswer: "dark brown"
    },

    {
        question: "What is not the main characteristic of arabica coffees?",
        answers:["sweeter", "low in caffeine", "light-bodied", "smaller beans"],
        correctAnswer: "smaller beans"
    },

    {
        question: "When coffee was discovered?",
        answers:["15th century", "16th century", "17th century", "19th century"],
        correctAnswer: "16th century"
    },

    {
        question: "What percentage of the coffee stays warm if we add cream to it??",
        answers:["10%", "20%", "30%", "if you have a microwave oven, always"]
        correctAnswer: "20%"
    },

    {
        question: "In which country do people drink the most coffee?",
        answers:["USA", "Finland", "Russia", "Vietnam"],
        correctAnswer: "Finland"
    }
]